(Leonard:)Oh, careful.
(Leonard:)That's my original series
Battlestar Galactica flight suit.
(Penny:)Oh, why didn't you wear it
on Halloween?
(Leonard:)Because it's not a costume.
It's a flight suit.
Okay, all right. Moving on.
(Penny:)Oh, wow, a paisley shirt.
(Leonard:)Uh-huh, it goes with my corduroy suit.
(Penny:)If you mean it should end up
in the same place, then I agree.
Is this your only tie?
(Leonard:)Ah, technically, yes.
(Leonard:)But if you'll notice, it's reversible.
(Leonard:)So it works as two.
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie,
I don't even think it works as one.
(Penny:)- Is this all your clothes?
- Yup, everything since the eighth grade.
(Penny:)The eighth grade?
(Leonard:)My last growth spurt.
(Penny:)Okay, well,
guess we're back to the corduroy suit.
- Great.
- Yup.